# **GULKAIYR KALYBEK KYZY**

### PL SQL DEVELOPER

🔀 gulkayir92@gmail.com 🔋 +996999404855 , whats app: +996708182346

Yurgyzstan, Bishkek in https://www.linkedin.com/in/gulkaiyr-kalybek-kyzy-387b7610a/

# **SUMMARY**

**Oracle PL/SQL** Developer with 3 years of experience in Analysis, Design, and Implementation of Custome Applications using the Oracle Relational Database Management System (RDBMS). Ability to work as an independent or as part of a team. Highly skilled and experienced PL SQL Developer with programs and procedures.

## **SKILLS**

Qracle (SQL, PL/SQL)	Oracle Form Builder	
HTML5, CSS	Oracle Workflow Builder	
SQL Developer	Java Scrtipt , xml	
WORDPRESS	TOAD	

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **SQL** Developer

#### KyrgyzKomerts Bank Feb 2022

- Participated in Analysis, Design, and Implementation of Business Applications using the Oracle (RDBMS).
- Expertise in Oracle 11g/10g, PL/SQL,SQL \*PLUS, TOAD and SQL DEVELOPER.
- Effectively made use of Table Functions, Indexes, Table Partitioning, Collections, Analytical functions, Materialized Views.
- Created Tables, Views, Constraints, Index (B Tree, Bitmap and Function Based).
- Developed Complex database objects like Stored Procedures, Functions, Packages and Triggers using SQL and PL/SQL.
- Experience in Oracle supplied packages, Dynamic SQL, Records and PL/SQL Tables.
- Worked extensively on Ref Cursor, External Tables and Collections.
- Expertise in Dynamic SQL, Collections and Exception handling.
- Good knowledge of Query Optimizer, Execution Plans, and Indexes.
- Creating new diagrams on Oracle Workflow Builder

#### Junior PL/SQL developer

## Demir Kyrgyz International Bank/ C technology Jul 2019 - Feb 2022

- Oracle Form Builder application development
- Oracle 11g/10g, PL/SQL,SQL \*PLUS
- TOAD and SQL DEVELOPER.

#### Internship

## WFL Publisher - Finland , Helsinki Jul 2017 - Dec 2017

- Graphic designer
- Content fuller
- Web developer

## Web site developer

Freelancer May 2018 - Present

#### Doing web sites

- www.kyrgyzwonders.com/
- www.kyrgyzshepherds.com/
- www.fizlab.manas.edu.kg/

#### Administrator

Citey Net *May 2012 - Sep 2013* 

Manager of internet club Cholpon-Ata, Kyrgyzstan "City Net" internet club

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Bronze medallist and Two-time Participant of the republican Olympiad in physics Kyrgyzstan, Bishkek
- Volunteer of The Congress of Women of the Kyrgyz Republic (with certificate) Kyrgyzstan, Bishkek
- Participant of Co-Opinion 3rd Annual Youth Summit (with certificate)Turkey, Istanbul

## **EDUCATION**

Masters of Computer and Information Engineering

University of Sakarya - Turkey, Sakarya Sep 2015 - Mar 2019

**Bachelors of Applied Math and Informatic** 

Kyrgyz Turkish Manas University - Kyrgyzstan, Bishkek Sep 2010 - Jun 2015

## **LANGUAGES**

English	Russian	
Turkish	Kyrgyz	

## **HOBBIES**

Reading Books	Codding
Playing Chess	Travelling